bootableusb.net 2017-11-30

# Privacy - Bootable USB | Bootable USB

1\. **Protecting your privacy** is very important to BootableUSB, and this statement is intended to make you aware of our commitments to you as an important visitor to our website. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

2\. **Scope of the Privacy Policy**. This Privacy Policy applies only to the collection and use of information collected online on the BootableUSB Website. Other websites that may be affiliated with BootableUSB may have different privacy policies.

3\. **Information**. We may collect your personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) when you visit the BootableUSB Website. Personal Information, however, is not collected on this website unless you choose to provide it to us. When making inquiries, ordering a product or requesting service information, participating in certain promotional activities, completing surveys, and generally corresponding with us, we may ask for certain Personal Information, including, for example, your name, mailing address, phone number and email address. If you are on a part of our website that requires you to provide your Personal Information, it will be clear what Personal Information we are requesting. We may also collect other information that is provided to us by your web browser. This may include the browser you used to come to our website, the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) of the website that you just visited before visiting our website, which pages on our website you visit, any search terms you entered, which URL you go to next, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address.

4\. **Children’s privacy**. If you are under the age of 18, please make sure that you provide your Personal Information only after obtaining your parental consent.

5\. **Protecting your Personal Information**. While BootableUSB does not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur, BootableUSB does take care in maintaining the security of your Personal Information and in preventing unauthorized access to it.

6\. **External Links.** In order to provide visitors with greater value, BootableUSB may provide links to various third party Web sites. However, even if a third-party affiliation exists between BootableUSB and that destination site, BootableUSB exercises no authority over linked sites, each of which maintains independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. BootableUSB assumes no responsibility or liability for these independent methods or actions and is not responsible for the independent policies or procedures of destination sites. Similarly, BootableUSB cannot take responsibility for the privacy initiatives or the content of such Web sites. These destination links are provided only for your convenience, and as such, you access them at your own risk.

7\. **Changes to this Statement**. BootableUSB reserves the right to change this Online Privacy Statement at any time. Any such changes will be posted in this Privacy Statement.

8\. **Applicable laws**. Bootable USB will protect your Personal Information in accordance with the United Kingdom laws.

9\. **IP Addresses**. An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. BootableUSB collects IP addresses in order to conduct system administration, and to conduct site analysis. To maintain visitor anonymity, BootableUSB does not associate IP addresses with records containing personal information.

10\. **Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie** :  
* Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

11\. **We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website**. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to·not having this information used by these companies, click here.

12\. [**Contact us**](http://bootableusb.net/contact-us/ "Contact US"). Please contact the webmaster through the “Contact Us” section if you have any questions or comments about the above.
